Hannah: Don’t you usually look before you cross the road?
I nearly hit you.
I didn’t see you until the last moment.
Jamie: Sorry! Hey, Hannah, it’s me.
It’s Jamie.
Hannah: Jamie! What are you doing here? I nearly killed you!
Jamie: I was buying something.
I was in a hurry and I crossed the road without looking.
Hannah: Come on.
Get in!
Waiter: Here you are.
Two cappuccinos.
Hannah and Jamie: Thanks.
Hannah: What an evening! I nearly killed you.
Jamie: Well, you didn’t kill me, so what’s the problem?
Hannah: But what were you doing there I thought you were here, in the café, waiting for me.
Jamie: I went to the theatre to buy these tickets for the Pink concert.
I know you wanted to go.
And it’s on the fifteenth of October – next Saturday.
Our anniversary.
Hannah: Our anniversary?
Jamie: Yes. Three months since we first met.
We met on Saturday the fifteenth of July. Remember?
Hannah: Gosh, Jamie.
I can’t believe you remember the exact day!
What a romantic! It’s lucky I didn’t hit you in the street…